sendearnings.com 2017-07-06

# SendEarnings® - Earn Cash for E-Mail, Surveys, Games, and More!

SendEarnings® reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. The date and time of the last update will always appear below, which serves as notice to our Users. All terms not defined in this Privacy Policy are as defined in our Terms and Conditions. This Privacy Policy applies to our provision of the Service Platforms and information collected through the Service Platforms. 

The column on the right provides a short explanation of the privacy policy and is not legally binding.

Last Updated: _February 10, 2016_

## I. INFORMATION COLLECTION

  1. #### Information Collected

All Users must provide the personally identifiable information requested in the sign-up or similar form in order to join SendEarnings®. Users may be required to provide subsequent demographic information in order to receive Signup Bonus(es) and/or qualify for other promotions. Demographic information includes, but is not limited to: birth date, gender, marital status, education completed, household income, and number of children in household. We may also ask you to provide on an optional and voluntary basis information regarding health and wellness issues relevant to you or your family, or information regarding you physical location (geo-tracking). To participate in certain activities or to enjoy certain functionalities, you must also agree to and permit certain tracking and automated information collection practices as described in this Privacy Policy. 

  2. #### Means of Collection

Users may join SendEarnings® by completing one of our signup forms, through Co-Registration, or other means as we may determine at any time in the future. Information is collected by SendEarnings® through a variety of methods, including: information the Member provides by filling out a form or submitting information through some other method; information that is collected through technological methods, such as “Cookies” or similar tracking technologies including geo-tracking; information received from third parties, for example if you complete a survey, the survey-company may inform us that you completed the survey. We also automatically collect, and may share with third parties, unique device identification numbers, as well as information about the type (brand / model) of device you use to access the Service Platform. SendEarnings® also includes multiple third party SDK’s within the Service Platform for multiple purposes, including to track which Members complete certain activities. Cookies and other recording, monitoring and tracking technologies, including persistent identifiers that may be placed on your computer, or other technologies including geo-tracking, are collectively referred to as “Cookies and Recording Tools.” 

in short:

You must provide basic demographic information to use SendEarnings®. Additional demographic data may be collected in order to improve your experience with the program.

## II. USE OF INFORMATION

  1. #### Use of Information

User information is used by SendEarnings® in all of the following ways: 

    1. E-Mail Address is used to send paid email advertisements and important announcements about SendEarnings® to User 
    2. All contact or similar information regarding you may be used to communicate to you as well as to track and record your activity, including but not limited to email, traditional mail, text, mobile telephone number, traditional / land telephone number, fax, social media account, any messaging / communication service, app, or tool including “push” notifications or similar. You understand and agree that, depending upon your individual arrangement with your telecommunication provider(s), receiving such communications may use data from your data-allowance and/or may result in fees owing by you to your telecommunications provider. 
    3. Mailing Address is used to send payments earned by User or otherwise communicate with User
    4. Demographic information is used to target advertisements to User
    5. Username, E-Mail Address, and Password are used for User protection to restrict access to their account 
    6. User information may be sold or disclosed to third parties as described in Sections II.2 and III below 
    7. Cookies and Recording Tools or similar tracking technology may be used as described in Section IV below 
    8. Information may be used in additional ways as posted on this Privacy Policy in the future.
  2. #### Sharing of Information

SendEarnings® does not rent, sell, or share User information, except in the following circumstances: 

    1. We are required, or believe it is in our interest, to release User information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal processes 
    2. Part or all of our business is sold to, merged with, or acquired by another company, in which case some or all User information would then belong to said company 
    3. We share User information when co-registration boxes (explained below) are checked during the course of registration 
    4. We suspect a User of committing fraud, in which case User information may be shared during the course of our investigation 
    5. We may sell or share User information to other advertisers or businesses whom we believe you may find useful and in order to enhance the service provided to our Users 
    6. We may share User information with third parties as reasonably necessary for us to operate the Service Platform and to provide offers and services to Users 
    7. California Residents Only: If you are a California resident, you have the right to receive: (i) information identifying any third party company(ies) to whom we may have disclosed, within the past calendar year, personal information pertaining to you for the company’s direct marketing purposes; and (ii) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed. To obtain such information you must make a request in writing to Customer Service using the contact information provided Section V of this Privacy Policy. 

in short:

We will use your email address to send you PaidEmails®, your home address to mail your check, and other collected demographic information to personalize our emails and Service Platform for you. 

## III. CO-REGISTRATION

  1. #### Definition

SendEarnings® signup pages may contain co-registration checkboxes, where Users can choose to “co-register” for other websites, tools, or services during their registration with SendEarnings® by checking the checkbox next to the co-registration Offer. Users are not required to select any co-registration boxes to join SendEarnings®; however, they may be required to do so in order to qualify for Signup Bonus(es) and/or other promotions. 

  2. #### Information Sharing

When a User co-registers for an Offer by checking the co-registration checkbox, any information they provide to SendEarnings® may be shared with the Advertiser associated with the co-registration Offer. SendEarnings® cannot control what Advertisers subsequently do with that information. 

  3. #### Privacy on Other Sites and Within Third Party Frames

The Service Platform may contain links to third party websites, services, or tools. Similarly, the Service Platform may contain framed / webview content from a third party. We provide these links and framed / webview content for your convenience. We do not review, control or monitor the privacy practices of websites, services or tools operated by others. We are not responsible for the performance of these sites, services or tools or for your business dealings with them. Your use of other websites, services, or third party tools is subject to the terms and conditions of those third party items, including the privacy policies of those websites, services, and/or/ third party tools. 

in short:

Our Advertisers each have their own Privacy Policies.

## IV. COOKIES AND THIRD PARTY TRACKING TECHNOLOGY

  1. #### About Cookies and Third Party Technology.

A “cookie” is a small data file that may be saved to and stored on your computer when you visit a website or similar technology or open an email. Cookies permit a website or similar technology operator to “remember” whether your computer has visited the website, tool or service before and helps the operator create a more personalized experience for you and records activities taken by you, such as offers completed. (In all cases in this Privacy Policy, the word “computer” includes all forms and styles of computing technologies including but not limited to desktop computers, laptop computers, tablet devices, smart-phones, other mobile or wearable computing technology.) 

In addition to cookie technology, SendEarnings® and our Advertisers use additional third party technology and tracking tools to record offers and activities completed by you, friends referred by you, and to communicate information about you, such as demographic information (e.g., age, gender), in order to target offers and advertisements to specific groups as requested by Advertisers. These items are referred to as “Cookies and Recording Tools” as further described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy. 

Your computer, tablet, smart-phone or similar device should permit you to change the settings on your web browser to not accept and/or disable Cookies and Recording Tools. However, if you do not accept Cookies and Recording Tools used by SendEarnings® and our Advertisers, you may not be able to use certain functions on certain websites, services or tools. More importantly, if you do not accept Cookies and Recording Tools you will not receive credit for offers or other actions completed by you because we and our Advertisers are unable to track and record your activity. If you do not want to accept Cookies and Recording Tools, you must stop using the Service Platform. 

  2. #### Third Party Cookies

Notwithstanding anything else in this policy, we or a data provider we have engaged may place or recognize a unique Cookie and/or Recording Tool on your browser or elsewhere on your computing device to enable you to receive customized ads or content. These Cookies and Recording Tools contain no personally identifiable information. The Cookies and Recording Tools may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us, e.g., your email address, that we may share with a data provider solely in hashed, non-human readable form. To opt-out of these Cookies and Recording Tools, please go to [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices). 

  3. #### Referral and Affiliate Tracking

SendEarnings® uses Cookies and Recording Tools in order to track new User registrations. This ensures Users are properly credited for referring other Users, as well as to track earnings for our Affiliates. 

  4. #### User Recognition

After a User has logged into the SendEarnings® Member’s Section, Cookies and Recording Tools are used to remember their Username and Password so they do not need to be entered during every visit to the Service Platform. Users can logout of the Member’s Section if they do not wish to have this information saved. 

  5. #### Location (Geo) Tracking

From time to time, SendEarnings® may permit Members to participate in activities, or provide offers, that involve use of location tracking / geo-tracking technology, that will share the physical location of a Member’s computer or mobile device. For example, we may contract with a market research firm that would track a Member’s physical location through geo-tracking / mobile technology for market research purposes. A Member may choose to opt-out or opt-in to this experience and offer. If the individual opts-in, the Member agrees to permit location-tracking, and also may be required to agree to the terms of service of such third party. If a Member opts-in to location (geo) tracking, SendEarnings® may then share such information with any/all the third parties with whom it does business that request such information. 

in short:

Our cookies, geo Location, and other tracking mechanisms are used in part to ensure you receive credit from our partners & affiliates.
